imagenar.com 2002-10-16

# ImagenAR, LLC - Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for imagenar.com 

**imagenar.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ imagenar.com ](http://www.imagenar.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. IP address data is also sometimes used to track demographics on hits from different top level domains. 

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies for other purposes. These are only related to issues such as window display settings and other look and feel issues, not for user tracking. 

####  Personal Information 

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **imagenar.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Web logs stored on our servers are protected and secure. However, they do not contain any personal information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
